Guide to the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Records, 1868-1991 bulk (1981-1990)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Files Series, 1967-1989, undated (bulk 1983-1987) (Box 35)
  - Office maintenance: Insurance, lease, 1982 (Box 38)
  - Ohio contacts, 1983 (Box 38)
  - Ohio Women's Opportunity in Road Construction Project, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Ohio Women's Opportunity in Road Construction: Tradeswomen meeting, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Organizational cycle, Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, undated (Box 38)
  - Organizational development: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1967-1987 (Box 38)
  - Parental leave, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Parental and Medical Leave Act of 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 38)
  - Parents Anonymous of Kentucky, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Pay policy: Administrative Policy Committee, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Personnel policies, 1982 (Box 38)
  - Policy decision, 1985-1987 (Box 38)
  - Poor and poverty, 1986 (Box 38)
  - Power, Sources of, 1986 (Box 38)
  - Powers, Georgia Davis, (Kentucky State Senator), 1981 (Box 38)
  - Press conference, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Press list: Women of the Rural South, 1986, June (Box 38)
  - Press release, 1980, Aug. (Box 38)
  - Press strategy workplan and releases, 1980-1984 (Box 38)
  - Program Development Committee, 1984-1987, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Project reporting updates, 1982-1984 (Box 39)
  - Proposal: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Legal Support Project, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Public Affairs Research and Communications, Inc., 1984-1987, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Racism: (Box 39)
    - Position papers by board members, 1982 (Box 39)
    - Racism/Sexist Workshop, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
  - Religious Network for Equality for Women, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Restaurant Employees Association of Lexington, Ky., 1983 (Box 39)
  - Right to work, 1986, Aug. (Box 39)
  - Roane-Calhoun Network, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Rural coalition: Jobs Task Force, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Rural women in poverty: Ford, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Single Mothers in a Learning Environment, 1983-1985 (Box 39)
  - Six month reports, 1980-1981 (Box 39)
  - South Carolina trip notes, 1982, May (Box 39)
  - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: (Box 39)
    - Board member recommitment policy, 1986, Apr. (Box 39)
    - Bylaws, 1978-1982 (Box 39)
  - Southern Black Women: Curriculum, undated (Box 39)
  - Southern Regional Conference Serving Rural Adults, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Southern Rural Women's Network, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Special reports: (Box 39)
    - "Employment in Road Construction; Who benefits?" 1983 (Box 39)
    - "Women and Road Construction," 1980-1982 (Box 39)
  - Speeches, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Staff memos, 1987-1989 (Box 39)
  - Staff retreat notes, 1985, Feb. (Box 39)
  - Staff search: Process notes, undated (Box 39)
  - Statement of principles: Board position papers, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Steering Committee composition, 1986 (Box 39)
  - Sudanese women: Rose Muraa, 1978-1982 (Box 39)
  - Sunnen Foundation, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Supreme Court hearing: Title VIII and sexual harassment, 1986 (Box 39)
  - Think tank outline; Southeast Women's Employment Coalition workplace, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Time sheets, 1984, July (Box 39)
  - Tradeswomen, 1984-1985 (Box 39)
  - Tradeswomen, Inc.: Conference material, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Transforming work, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Transitional Black Women's Project, Atlanta University, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Trip notes: (Box 39)
    - New York, 1982, July-1986, (3 folders) (Box 39)
    - Washington, D.C., 1983, (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - Washington, D.C. and New York, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Trip reports: Staff, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Unemployment in America, undated (Box 40)
  - United National Decade for Women: Information kit, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
  - United Tradeswomen, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Vacation requests, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Highway Consent Decree, 1983 (Box 40)
  - West Virginia Department of Transportation lawsuit, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Whitney, John Jay Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
  - Women and health issues, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
  - Women and the Law Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
  - Women and the vote, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
  - Women and vocational education, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Women Employed Institute, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Women for Economic Justice, 1985 (Box 40)
  - "Women in Construction," Federal Register, 1977-1980 (Box 40)
  - Women labor lawyers and legal workers, Washington, D.C., 1984 (Box 40)
  - Women's Development Corporation, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Women's economic development, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Women's issues: (Box 40)
    - 1980-1988 (Box 40)
    - Clippings, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Women's Research and Education Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 40)
  - Women's Technical Assistant Project: (Box 40)
    - 1982-1986 (Box 40)
    - New sources of funding, 1985 (Box 40)
    - Resource women meeting notes, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Women's Workforce Network, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Women's World Conference, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Work plans, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
  - Working assets, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Workshops: (Box 40)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Jobs Program, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
    - Economics Training, 1983, June, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Federally Employed Women: Women in Nontraditional Jobs, 1983 (Box 40)
    - Job Training Partnership Act, 1983, Feb. 18 (Box 40)
    - Leadership and Mastery, 1985, undated (Box 40)
    - Women in the 80s, 1981 (Box 40)
    - Women and the Unions, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Youth Project: (Box 40)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 40)
    - Unemployment, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous: (Box 40)
    - 1980-1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Clippings, 1988 (Box 40)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 40)
    - Title IX, 1987 (Box 40)
- Proposals Series, 1971-1991, undated (bulk 1983-1988) (Box 40)
  Financial reports, correspondence, project proposal summary sheets, and notes chiefly pertaining to various organizations, companies, and foundations the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition applied to for financial support. Arranged alphabetically by funding agency.
  - Aetna Life and Casualty, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc., 1987 (Box 40)
  - Apple Computer, 1983-1984 (Box 40)
  - Aspen Institute, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Atlantic Telephone and Telegraph Foundation, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Babcock Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
  - Beasley Foundation, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Black Women's National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Project, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Campaign for Human Development, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Center for Education and Communication, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Coalition on Human Needs, 1983-1987 (Box 40)
  - Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1988 (Box 40)
  - Container Corporation of America, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Disciples of Christ, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Discount Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 41)
  - Economic Development Administration, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Economic Justice for Women Conference, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Economics Project, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Ecumenical Review Board, 1987 (Box 41)
  - Field Foundation, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Ford Economics Project, 1982-1984 (Box 41)
  - Ford Foundation, 1982-1990, (7 folders) (Box 41)
  - Fund for Southern Communities, 1983-1984 (Box 41)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post Secondary Education, 1983-1986 (Box 41)
  - Funding Exchange, 1985-1987 (Box 41)
  - Greater Resources and Opportunities for Women, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 41)
  - Hearst Foundation, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Highlander Research Program, undated (Box 41)
  - Jewish Fund for Justice, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Joyce Foundation, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Jubliee Fund, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Kellogg Fellowship, 1985-1986 (Box 41)
  - Leadership Program, 1982-1984, (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Levi Strauss Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 41)
  - Lutheran Church, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Lutheran Development Assistance, 1985 (Box 41)
  - Lutheran World Relief Fund, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Mercy Action Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 41)
  - Metro Atlanta Community Foundation, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Minority Business Enterprise: Kentucky State Government, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Mott, Charles Stewart Foundation, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Mountain Association for Community Economic Development, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Ms. Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 41)
  - National Committee on the Self-Development of People, 1983 (Box 41)
  - National Technical Assistance Program, 1987 (Box 41)
  - Needmor Fund, 1983-1986 (Box 41)
  - Needmor Fund, 1983-1986 (Box 42)
  - New York Community Trust, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Norman Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 42)
  - Pallottines Immaculate Conception Province, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Playboy Foundation, 1983 (Box 42)
  - Poverello Fund, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Presbyterian Hunger Fund, 1982-1989 (Box 42)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Reconciliation Fund, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Restaurant Employees Association of Lexington, Ky.: Special project, 1983-1984 (Box 42)
  - Revson, Charles Foundation, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1985-1989, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Rural Justice Project, 1982 (Box 42)
  - Sisters of Loretto, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Sisters of Mercy Health Corporation, 1986 (Box 42)
  - The Sophia Fund, 1988 (Box 42)
  - Southern Appalachian Leadership Training, 1978-1982, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Southern Neighborhoods, 1982 (Box 42)
  - State of Black Arkansas Project, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Unitarian Universalist social concerns: (Box 42)
    - 1984-1988 (Box 42)
    - Grants-making panel, 1985-1987 (Box 42)
  - United Church of Christ, 1982-1985, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - United States Department of Commerce: Economic Development Administration (Box 42)
    - 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - United Zipper Company, 1983 (Box 42)
  - Veatch Program, 1983-1985 (Box 42)
  - Wellspring Fund, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Whitney, John Hay Foundation, 1983 (Box 42)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women, 1983 (Box 42)
  - Women and Enterprise, 1983 (Box 42)
  - Women and the New Federalism: (Box 42)
    - 1982 (Box 42)
    - Redirecting strategies for change, undated (Box 42)
  - Women in the Eighties Project, 1982 (Box 42)
  - Women's Commission in Exile, 1982 (Box 42)
  - Women's Educational Equity Act Program, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Women's Empowerment Project, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Women's Opportunity Giving Fund, 1980-1986 (Box 42)
  - Women's Southern Dollars Campaign, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Women's Technical Assistance Project, 1982-1984 (Box 42)
  - Youth Project, 1986-1988 (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous: (Box 43)
    - 1979-1991, (6 folders) (Box 43)
    - Background information, 1974-1980 (Box 43)
    - Draft, 1983-1988 (Box 43)
    - Economic strategy, 1982 (Box 43)
    - General proposal, 1983 (Box 43)
    - General support, 1981-1987, undated, (4 folders) (Box 43)
    - Network language, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Original, 1981 (Box 43)
    - Proposal letters, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition proposal, 1980, Mar. (Box 43)
- Project Files Series, 1970-1990, undated (bulk 1983-1988) (Box 43)
  Correspondence, reports, meeting minutes, clippings, and mailing lists relating to various projects with which the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition was involved. Arranged in alphabetical order by name of project.
  - Coal Employment Project, 1980-1988 (Box 43)
  - Economics Research Project: (Box 43)
    - Administration: (Box 43)
      - Alabama, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
      - North Carolina, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
      - South Carolina, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
      - West Virginia: (Box 43)
        - Central, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
        - Southern, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
    - Administrative: (Box 43)
      - Coordinators' general correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
      - State coordinator's job description and administrative organization, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Development design: (Box 43)
      - Initial project planning, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
      - Overall design, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
      - Statewide data base, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
    - Evaluations, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
    - Questionnaire analysis, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
    - Regional meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 44)
    - Summaries: Progress reports, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
    - Summaries: Work plans, 1983-1984 (Box 44)
    - Support information request letters, 1983-1985 (Box 44)
  - International Community Leadership Project: (Box 44)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
    - Information contact list, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Networking Communications Committee, 1983, undated (Box 44)
    - New York agenda, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Resource materials, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
    - Statement of solidarity, 1983 (Box 44)
  - Leadership Development Program: (Box 44)
    - 1988 (Box 44)
    - Applications, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Career track workbook, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Charleston women's group, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Committee, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Curriculum, undated (Box 44)
    - Hardeeville (S.C.) education group, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Minutes, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Petersfield Human Services, Yonges Island, S.C., 1985-1987 (Box 44)
    - Proposal, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Research and education, 1986-1987 (Box 44)
    - Sea Island players, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
    - Sew and Sew Crop, 1987-1988 (Box 44)
    - Work plans, 1986-1987 (Box 44)
    - Workshop evaluation forms, undated (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1988, undated (Box 44)
  - National Unemployed Network, 1986-1988, undated (Box 44)
  - North American International Leadership Project Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
  - Planning and Management Assistance Project, 1977-1983 (Box 44)
  - Research projects, 1984-1986 (Box 44)
  - Rural Justice Project, 1983 (Box 44)
  - Rural Youth and Women's projects, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Tourism: (Box 44)
    - Budget and expenses, 1986-1988 (Box 44)
    - Center for Responsible Tourism, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Clippings, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Committee meetings, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Committee members: Research and education overview, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Conference, 1987, (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - Conference flyers, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence: Contracts, 1986-1988 (Box 44)
    - Funding information, 1987-1988 (Box 45)
    - Notes: Sevier County, Tennessee (Box 45)
    - Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 45)
    - Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 45)
    - Research and education, 1987 (Box 45)
    - Tourism director orientation, 1987-1988 (Box 45)
    - Writings: Behind the Glitter: (Box 45)
      - Background, 1988 (Box 45)
      - Book orders, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 45)
      - Draft, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Galleys, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Publicity: (Box 45)
        - Commercial television stations, undated (Box 45)
        - Kentucky News Media Directory, 1986 (Box 45)
        - Mailing lists, undated, (2 folders) (Box 45)
        - Newspapers, undated (Box 45)
        - Public education radio stations, undated (Box 45)
        - State government, 1988 (Box 45)
        - Tennessee advocacy groups, 1989 (Box 45)
        - Tennessee public radio stations: Commercial radio stations, undated (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1988, (4 folders) (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box 46)
  - Women and Poverty Project, undated (Box 46)
  - Women of the Rural South publication: (Box 46)
    - Ads/marketing: (Box 46)
      - Distribution, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
      - Flyer: Contacts, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Copyright, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
    - Media: Public Affairs Research and Communications, Inc.: (Box 46)
      - Media coverage: Articles, 1986-1988 (Box 46)
      - Press releases and contacts, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Production: (Box 46)
      - Bills/budget, 1985-1986 (Box 46)
      - Graphics/printing, 1985, undated (Box 46)
      - Photographs, 1985-1986 (Box 46)
      - Typesetting and printing, 1985 (Box 46)
    - States: Ford Report: (Box 46)
      - North Carolina, undated (Box 46)
      - South Carolina, undated (Box 46)
      - West Virginia, undated (Box 46)
      - Overview section; text, 1984 (Box 46)
      - Text, 1985-1986 (Box 46)
  - Women's Action Agenda, 1985 (Box 46)
  - Women's Economic Agenda Project, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Women's Economic Development Project, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Women's Media Project, 1985-1986 (Box 46)
  - Women's Technical Assistance Project: (Box 46)
    - Excerpts from A Background on Women and Work in the Southeast, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Planning and budget, 1971-1987 (Box 46)
    - Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
    - Resource guide to church funding sources, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Workshop: Skills-sharing, 1984, May (Box 46)
    - Workshops, 1984-1987, (2 folders) (Box 46)
- Highways Projects Files Series, 1970-1989, undated (bulk 1983-1987) (Box 46)
  Correspondence, clippings, newsletters, mailing lists, reports, and training brochures. Arranged into two subseries: United States and State Departments of Transportation, and Alphabetical Files. Files under United States and State Departments of Transportation are arranged chronologically and then alphabetically. Alphabetical Files are arranged in alphabetical order by topic. Some files pertaining to the Women's Opportunities in Road Construction Project are found in this series.
  - United States and State Departments of Transportation Subseries (Box 46)
    - United States Department of Transportation: (Box 47)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 47)
      - Complaint, 1984 (Box 47)
      - Complaint procedures, 1977 (Box 47)
      - Correspondence (Incoming), 1975-1980 (Box 47)
      - Freedom of Information Act request, 1977-1989 (Box 47)
      - Meetings, 1983-1988, (2 folders) (Box 47)
      - Research and Evaluation Associates, Inc., 1989 (Box 47)
    - State Departments of Transportation: (Box 47)
      - 1980 (Box 47)
      - Correspondence (Incoming), 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 47)
      - Equal Economic Opportunity specialists, 1980 (Box 47)
      - Federal Aid workforce profiles, 1976-1983 (Box 47)
      - Internal workforce profiles (Equal Economic Opportunity), 1976-1981 (Box 47)
      - Reports, 1984 (Box 47)
      - Statistics, 1985 (Box 47)
    - State Departments of Transportation: Specific States: (Box 47)
      - California, 1984-1988, undated, (6 folders) (Box 47)
      - Georgia, 1976-1985 (Box 47)
      - Kentucky, 1980-1988, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - Maryland, 1984-1986, (3 folders) (Box 48)
      - Missouri, 1983-1987, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - New York, 1982-1985, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - North Carolina, 1980 (Box 48)
      - Ohio, 1984-1987, undated, (4 folders) (Box 48)
      - Tennessee, 1980 (Box 48)
      - Virginia, 1980-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - West Virginia, 1978-1980, undated (Box 48)
  - Alphabetical Subseries (Box 48)
    - Administrative complaint; United States Department of Labor; United States Department of Transportation, 1980-1986, (6 folders) (Box 49)
    - Congressional hearings, 1984-1988, (4 folders) (Box 49)
    - Federal Highway Administration: (Box 49)
      - Division correspondence: (Box 49)
        - Incoming, 1975-1980 (Box 49)
        - Outgoing, 1980 (Box 49)
      - Five most active Federal Highway Administration contractors, 1980 (Box 49)
      - National correspondence: Freedom Of Information Act denial, 1980-1981 (Box 49)
      - National office correspondence: Incoming, 1980-1981 (Box 49)
      - Regional correspondence: Incoming, 1980 (Box 49)
      - Statistics, 1977-1980 (Box 49)
      - Steppe Associates complaint, 1980 (Box 49)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1979-1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Freedom of Information Act: (Box 50)
      - 1979-1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 50)
      - Request, 1984-1985 (Box 50)
      - State responses, 1979-1980, (3 folders) (Box 50)
    - Highway Act of 1986, 1986 (Box 50)
    - Highway employment: General, 1981-1983 (Box 50)
    - Laws, 1970-1988 (Box 50)
    - Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs, Department of Labor: (Box 50)
      - Correspondence (Incoming), 1981 (Box 50)
      - Highways complaint file, 1981 (Box 50)
      - Monitoring data, 1979-1980 (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 50)
    - Proposals: (Box 50)
      - General support and Women's Opportunity in Road Construction funds, 1987-1989 (Box 50)
      - Highways: (Box 50)
        - 1981-1984 (Box 50)
        - Ford Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 50)
        - Project funding leads, 1984 (Box 50)
      - Levi Strauss Women's Opportunity in Road Construction Highways proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 50)
      - Needmor Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 50)
      - Women and work research, 1985-1986 (Box 50)
      - Women in road construction, 1981-1983 (Box 50)
      - Women's Asphalt Alliance Project, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Road construction: (Box 50)
      - Applying for a construction job, undated (Box 50)
      - Associated general contractors, 1980-1981 (Box 50)
      - Central Kentucky Support Group, 1981 (Box 50)
      - Clippings, 1980-1984, (2 folders) (Box 50)
      - Contract Compliance Workshop, 1980 (Box 50)
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 50)
      - Current jobs, 1981 (Box 50)
      - Employment in Road Construction: Who Benefits? 1981 (Box 50)
      - Finances, 1986 (Box 50)
      - Five most active road builders in the Southeast, 1980 (Box 50)
      - Greater Resources and Opportunities for Women, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
      - Highways: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 50)
      - Kentucky: (Box 50)
        - Contractors, 1987 (Box 50)
        - Planning committee, 1987 (Box 50)
        - Tradeswomen retreat, 1987 (Box 50)
      - Knoxville Support Group, 1981-1982 (Box 51)
      - Press conference, 1984, Oct. (Box 51)
      - Press packet, 1985 (Box 51)
      - Press releases, 1980-1982 (Box 51)
      - Questionnaires, 1980-1981 (Box 51)
      - Report, 1980-1981 (Box 51)
      - Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works, 1984 (Box 51)
      - Statistics, 1976-1979 (Box 51)
      - Training brochures: Non-trade groups, 1988 (Box 51)
      - Training materials, undated (Box 51)
      - Unions and women workers, 1979-1981 (Box 51)
      - Utilization of women by private highway contractors in federal aid highway construction projects, 1981 (Box 51)
      - Wage rates, 1985-1987 (Box 51)
      - Women in construction: (Box 51)
        - 1981 (Box 51)
        - Clippings, 1982 (Box 51)
        - Program, 1987 (Box 51)
        - Report, 1988 (Box 51)
      - Women's Asphalt Alliance: (Box 51)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 51)
        - Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 51)
        - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1981, undated (Box 51)
    - Women's Opportunity in Road Construction: (Box 51)
      - Advertisements, 1987, undated (Box 51)
      - Brochure, 1986 (Box 51)
      - Clippings, 1984-1988, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Correspondence: (Box 51)
        - Incoming, 1986-1989 (Box 51)
        - Outgoing, 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 51)
      - Newsletter, 1986, undated (Box 51)
      - Project program plan, 1988-1989 (Box 51)
      - Proposal, 1981-1986, undated (Box 51)
      - Responses to ads, 1981, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Strategy Committee, 1987-1989, undated (Box 52)
      - Women's Law Fellowship, 1983-1985 (Box 52)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1988, undated (Box 52)
    - Women's Opportunity in Road Construction: Specific States (Box 52)
      - Alaska, 1987 (Box 52)
      - Florida, 1987 (Box 52)
      - Georgia, 1986-1987 (Box 52)
      - Kentucky (Eastern), 1986-1989, undated (Box 52)
      - Ohio, 1984-1985, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - Virginia, 1983-1985, undated, (3 folders) (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous: (Box 52)
      - 1979-1988, undated (Box 52)
      - Apprenticeship programs, 1980 (Box 52)
      - Clippings, 1980-1987 (Box 52)
      - Equal Economic Opportunity: Calls, information, 1989, undated (Box 52)
      - Feeney vs. Massachusetts: Veterans preference challenge, 1984 (Box 52)
      - Gas Tax Act of 1983: Legislation and report, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Mailing lists, undated (Box 52)
      - Support letters, 1983-1985 (Box 52)